Guide to the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America records, 1914-1980.
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America records, 1914-1980.
- VI. Records of joint boards and local unions, 1914-1970. (Box 37-65)
  - C. Records of joint boards and local unions, 1931-1970.
    - Baltimore Joint Board. Extracts from Hearing of Garment Workers conducted by Dr. Jacob H. Hollander in Baltimore, October 13, 1932 (Box 57, Folder 9-10)
    - Boston Joint Board. Correspondence of Manager Joseph Salerno, 1936-41 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Buffalo Joint Board, 1937-40 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Button Division. Correspondence of Local 289 (Muscatine, Iowa) President Vernon Dale, 1941 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Chicago Joint Board (miscellaneous correspondence) 1931-51 (Box 57, Folder 14-15)
    - Cincinnati Joint Board. Correspondence of Manager Jack Kroll re Shirt Workers organizing campaign, 1935-41 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Cleveland Joint Board. Correspondence of Manager Ben Peppercorn, 1941-42 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Cleaners and Dyers (1937) Julius Cohen, secretary (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Dallas, Texas (summary of organizing tactics) 1940 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Davenport, Iowa, Local 264, 1937 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Delaware and Maryland Joint Board (Shirt Workers Local 237) 1937 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Elizabeth, N.J., Local 126, 1939-40 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Fall River, Mass. Supplementary Statement to Arbitrator on issues involved in dispute between Amalgamated Clothing Workers and Anderson Little Company, December 4, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Ft. Wayne, Indiana Local 146. Letter from Dorothy Palmer to Joseph Schlossberg, February, 1937 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Glove Workers correspondence with Joseph Schlossberg re 1937 organizing campaign in New York City, Gloversville, N.Y. and Toledo, Ohio. (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Greenbay, Wisconsin, 1937 (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Indianapolis, Ind. (1940) Local 145 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Italian Locals 144, Chicago, 51 Baltimore, 1930 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Jacksonville, Illinois, Local 199, 1939 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Journeymen Tailors Union (1936-41) including 1940 convention proceeding (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Kansas City (clippings and miscellaneous papers) 1923-32 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Kentucky Joint Board. Correspondence of Robert Hardy and Newman Jeffrey of Local 98 re Paducah Shirt Workers organizing campaign, 1937 (Box 58, Folder 17-18)
    - Kingston, North Carolina, letters of rank and file workers describing conditions in the Shirt factories, 1943 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - La Follette, Tennessee, Local 95 (extracts from minutes) 1940-45 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - La Follette, Local 95, Executive Board Minutes, May 26, 1938 - October 4, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - La Follette, Local 95, Executive Board Minutes, June 14, 1944 - July 18, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - La Follette, Local 95 (monthly shop meetings) July 21, 1942 - October 2, 1945 (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Laundry Workers Joint Board. Correspondence and papers, 1937-39 including correspondence re 1938 appointment of Walter Cook as Manager and his replacement in 1939 by Louis Simon (Box 59, Folder 1-2)
    - Laundry Workers Joint Board. Survey of Earnings of Commission Family Laundry Drivers in the New York Area (ACWA Research Dept., May 1945) (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Los Angeles Joint Board. Miscellaneous papers, 1926-30 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Louisville, Kentucky, Local 120. Emma Saurer's correspondence with Sidney Hillman, 1938 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Maryland, Virginia, Pennsylvania Regional Joint Board (clipping) (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Martinsberg, West Virginia, Local 1756, 1936 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Minnesota Joint Board. Correspondence with Sander Genis, Manager, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Montreal Joint Board, 1937-40 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Nashville, Tennessee. Shirt Workers Organizing Campaign, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 10-12)
    - Neckwear Makers Union (1936) including Public Hearing - Industrial Homework, Men's Neckwear Industry (New York State Dept. of Labor) (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - New Albany, Indiana (1937) Locals 87 and 244 (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - New Bedford, Mass. (Organizing the Shirt Workers) 1937 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - New Castle, Pennsylvania, 1937 (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - New Haven, Ct. (Organizing the Shirt Workers of Local 125) correspondence of Aldo Cursi, 1935-42 (Box 59, Folder 17-18)
    - New Jersey Joint Board (South Jersey Jt. Bd.) 1923-52 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
    - New York Joint Board (1935-69) miscellaneous papers (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - New York Joint Board. Papers re Victor Allerprando Case, 1954 (Box 60, Folder 4-5)
    - New York Joint Board Corruption Hearings (April-May, 1933) Charges against B. Jackson, Trade Manager of the Coat Department, Hyman Siegel, J. Ginsburg and Silvi Silverman, Business Agents. (Box 60, Folder 6-8)
    - New York Joint Board Corruption Hearings (April-May 1933) collateral documents (Box 61, Folder 1-2)
    - Newburgh, N.Y., 1935 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Norfolk, Va., Local 92. Shirt Workers Organizing Campaign, correspondence of Edith Christenson, Willois Bishop (organizers) and others, 1934 (Box 61, Folder 4-8)
    - Norfolk, Va., correspondence of Jacob Potofsky, 1935 (Box 61, Folder 9-10)
    - Norfolk, Va., Excerpts from Court Testimony (1936) including correspondence with ACWA attorney Louis Waldman (Box 61, Folder 11-12)
    - Norfolk, Va., National Labor Relations Board. Correspondence, 1934 (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - Overalls Joint Board, including correspondence of Jacob Potofsky to Harry Rogen, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Pennsylvania Joint Board, including correspondence of Manager, David Monas, 1939-54 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Philadelphia Joint Board, 1920-37 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Pittsburgh Joint Board, 1939-52 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Poughkeepsie Local 123, 1937 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Richmond, Va., Local 88, Shirt Workers Organizing Campaign (1937), correspondence of Clemmie Shuck, organizer with Dorothy Bellanca and Jacob Potofsky (Box 62, Folder 6-8)
    - Rochester Joint Board (1935-47) including correspondence of Abe Chatman, manager re 1947 jurisdictional dispute with the International Ladies' Garment Workers Union (Box 62, Folder 9-10)
    - St. Louis Joint Board including correspondence of Ben Gilbert, manager with Jacob Potofsky re Shirt Workers organizing campaign, 1936-39 (Box 62, Folder 11-12)
    - Salesman Local 340, New York, New York, 1949 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - San Francisco Joint Board, 1935-38 (Box 63-64, Folder 14)
    - Schuylkill County (Report on 1920 organizing drive) (Box 63-64, Folder 1)
    - Shirt Workers Joint Board, 1933-40 (Box 63-64, Folder 2-4)
    - South Eastern Regional Joint Board (1939,1971) mostly newspaper clippings and organizing leaflets (Box 63-64, Folder 5)
    - Southwestern Regional Joint Board (organizing report) c.1955 (Box 63-64, Folder 6)
    - Springfield, Mass., Local 290, 1939 (Box 63-64, Folder 7)
    - Staunton, Va. (Shirt Workers organizing campaign, 1937). Correspondence of ACWA attorney Louis Waldman with Sidney Hillman and organizer Willois Bishop with Dorothy Jacobs Bellanca. (Box 63-64, Folder 8)
    - Syracuse, N.Y., Local 220, correspondence of local union president Philip L. Castro with Jacob Potofsky, 1941 (Box 63-64, Folder 9)
    - Toronto Joint Board, 1936-1969 (Box 63-64, Folder 10)
    - Utica, N.Y., 1933-42 (Box 63-64, Folder 11)
    - Vestmakers Union (Box 63-64, Folder 12)
    - Webster, Mass. Joint Board, 1938 (Box 63-64, Folder 13)
    - Winnipeg, Canada, 1946 (Box 63-64, Folder 14)
    - Worcester, Mass., 1941 (Box 63-64, Folder 15)
  - D. General correspondence file, 1913-1941, and charter applications from locals.
    - General Correspondence, 1913-41 (Box 65, Folder 1-11)
    - Charter applications (Box 65, Folder 12)
- VII. Sidney Hillman papers, 1930-1946. (Box 66-111)
  Sidney Hillman and the ACWA played crucial roles in founding the CIO. Hillman's correspondence with Walter Reuther and George Addes of the United Automobile Workers (UAW) and Emil Rieve of the Textile Workers' Organizing Committee reflects that effort.
  The Roosevelt era brought both increased visibility and power to Hillman and the union. In 1933, Hillman was chosen to serve on the National Recovery Administration's Labor Advisory Board. The materials from this NRA period describe the Roosevelt administration's attempts to draw up codes of fair competition to determine production quotas and fix wages and hours in order to bring about economic recovery. The NRA records also contain Hillman's correspondence with government officials as well as leaders of labor unions and of private firms. There are also some reports and raw data used by the NRA in developing its codes.
  In 1940, as U.S. involvement in World War II became increasingly likely, Roosevelt organized the National Defense Advisory Commission (NDAC) to coordinate economic mobilization for the war. Hillman was named to the Commission; later he was tapped to be associate director of the War Production Board. The NDAC materials in this collection document Hillman's experiences and include correspondence with William Knudsen. There are also some reports and directives prepared by the War Production Board.
  Other notable topics include: aid to free labor organizations in Europe during World War II; anti-fascist efforts by U.S.labor organizations; civil rights; the clothing trade in the U.S. and Canada; economic conditions during the depression, particularly in the U.S. garment industry; international labor activities; Jewish workers in Palestine; labor organizing in the U.S. and Canada; relations with other unions; the Spanish Civil War, including labor aid to and participation in the Republican cause; union involvement in politics and government in the U.S.; the role of women and minorities in the labor movement; and worker education.
  Notable individuals represented in the collection include: Mary Anderson; John B. Andrews; August Bellanca; Dorothy Bellanca; George Berry; S.M. Blinken; Louis Brandeis; Harry Bridges; John Brophy; Max Danish; Clarence Darrow; Gladys Dickason; David Dubinsky; Lillian Hellman; Charles J. Hendley; Arturo Giovannitti; Henry Green; William Green; J.B.S. Hardman; Bessie Hillman; Horace Kallen; Paul Kellogg; Philip La Follette; Robert La Follette; Fiorello LaGuardia; Herbert H. Lehman; John L. Lewis; Sinclair Lewis; Jay Lovestone; Homer Martin; Lucy Mason; Tom Mooney; Reinhold Niebuhr; Frances Perkins; Charles Poletti; Lee Pressman; Walter Reuther; Emil Rieve; Eleanor Roosevelt; Franklin D. Roosevelt; Rose Schneiderman; Upton Sinclair; Harry Truman; B.C. Vladeck; Robert F. Wagner; Henry Wallace; Walter White; and Matthew Woll.
  Additional organizations of significance represented include: local unions and joint boards of the ACWA; the American Civil Liberties Union; American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee; American League Against War and Fascism; the AFL; the CIO; the Fur and Leather Workers' Union; Hart, Schaffner, and Marx; Hickey Freeman and Company; the Jewish Daily Forward; the Journeymen Tailors Union; Labor's Non-Partisan League; the NAACP; the NRA; the Socialist Party (U.S.); the Steel Workers' Organizing Committee; the Textile Workers Organizing Committee; the Textile Workers Union of America; the UAW; the U.S. Department of Labor and its Women's Bureau; the Urban League; the Women's Trade Union League; and the Workmen's Circle.
  The papers from the early 1930s are extremely fragmentary; consequently, little material documenting the devastating effect of the early Depression years on the ACWA remains. The campaign to organize shirt and pants workers during the mid- to late 1930s is somewhat better documented, and is described by Hillman's correspondence with organizers in Rochester (N.Y.), Cincinnati, and Philadelphia.
  - A. Correspondence, 1930-46.
    - Abbott, Grace (Social Service Review, University of Chicago) 1936, Includes discussion of the Labor Department and aid to dependent children, Unemployment Insurance and the Security Act. (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Abt, John (ACWA attorney) 1938 amendments to the Wagner Act (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Adamic, Louis (American Committee for Yugoslav Relief) 1945, Contributions for an x-ray machine for tubercular children of Yugoslavia. (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Addams, Jane (Hull House) 1930, Suggestion that Grace Abbott be appointed Secretary of Labor. (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Addes, George (United Automobile Workers) 1938 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Affiliated School for Workers, 1938 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Agricultural Adjustment Administration, 1935-36, Includes discussion of the Resettlement Administration and homestead projects; the Department of Agriculture and "enlightened businessmen"; urban and rural women's discussion of the "problems facing the American home". (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Alabama State Industrial Union Council, 1940 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Allis Chalmers Workers, 1940 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Aluminum Workers of America (International Union) 1938 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Amalgamated Association of Iron, Steel and Tin Workers (Cleveland Lodge) 1939 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1936-38 convention invitations (Box 66, Folder 12-13)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers (general communications) 1938, ACWA's label (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Amalgamated Housing Corp., 1935 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Amalgamated Life Insurance, 1945 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Amalgamated Trust and Savings Bank (Chicago) 1936-45 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - American Academy of Political and Social Sciences, 1930 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - American Arbitration Association, 1938 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - American Association for Labor Legislation, 1935-38 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1936-37, Includes discussion of the Freedom of Air Bills; a committee to monitor the proceedings of the Joint Legislative Committee to investigate "subversive and un-American activities" in New York public schools and colleges; the Doyle-Neustein labor relations bills. (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - American Committee for the Protection of the Foreign Born, 1938, H.R. 9007 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - American Federation of Actors, 1935, Criticisms of the National Industrial Recovery Board's motion picture code (11pp.) (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - American Federation of Government Employees, 1935, Includes resolution calling for "the establishment of a government transfer agency for the purpose of transferring to other agencies government workers who are dismissed through no fault of their own"; essay, "Should College Graduation be required for Entrance into the Public Service" by E. Claude Babcock (President, American Federation of Government Employees.) (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - American Federation of Labor, 1935-36, 1940, Correspondence relating to AFL injunction proceedings against the Building Trades Department; Green's discussion of AFL organizations' endorsement of a "communist" sponsored meeting on Unemployment and Social Insurance; poor working conditions for women at the Reliance Manufacturing Company (6pp); "Minority Report of Resolutions Committee on Organization Policies" (3pp). (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - American Friends of the Soviet Union, 1936, Telegram requesting Hillman's attendance at a meeting to discuss Hitler. (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - American Fund for Political Prisoners and Refugees (George Novak) 1938, Letter to Prime Minister Negrin (Barcelona, Spain) requesting a public trial for CNT-FAI, UGT (Socialist Party and POUM member.) (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - American Labor Party (1936-45), Includes correspondence with Elinore Herrick, state campaign director. (Box 66, Folder 28-30)
    - American League Against War and Fascism, 1935-37 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - American Magazine, 1943 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - American Public Welfare Association, 1936 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - American Student Union (1937) includes correspondence with Joseph Lasch and James Wechsler, Includes discussion of the establishment of a CIO training school for recent college graduates. (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - American Youth Congress, 1936-40, Includes reports from Model Congress Committees on labor, civil liberties, Peace, education, agriculture and a Declaration of Rights of American Youth. (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - Ameringer, Oscar, 1936-40, The labor press (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - Anderson, Mary (Women's Bureau, U.S. Dept. of Labor) 1930-38, Suggestion that Grace Abbott be appointed Secretary of Labor; women workers at H.D. Bob Shirt Factory file complaint against employer and union representative. (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - Andrews, John B. (American Association for Labor Legislation) 1930-40, Includes discussion of unemployment bills; Unemployment Insurance Compensation; the Schwartzwald-Crews silicosis bill. (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - Anderson, Paul (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Anthracite Tri-District News, Includes 31 letters from J.W.Cooper High School students (Shenandoah, PA) to Dorothy Bellanca, Jacob Potofsky and Hillman requesting their assistance in reviving the anthracite coal industry. (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Apparel Codes Label Council (National Industrial Recovery Administration) 1935 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Applications (job) 1937-40, Applications for employment including one from Ruth (Schlossberg) Landes. (Box 67, Folder 4-5)
    - Associated Clothing Manufacturers, Inc., 1936 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Atlanta Federation of Trades, 1936 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Automobile Workers of America (United) 1937-39 including correspondence with Homer Martin, George Addes, and Walter Reuther, Correspondence and other documents relating to UAW factional difficulties. Mentioned are R.J. Thomas, ...Martin, George F. Addes, Philip Murray, John L. Lewis. Also farm implements situation in Wisconsin, technological unemployment, nationwide anti-CIO campaign, organizing victory at General Motors. (Box 67, Folder 8-12)
    - Automobile Workers of America (United) Local 248 & 249, Allis Chalmers, 1938, Correspondence concerning "warfare" on the UAW at the Ford plant (Kansas City, MO); procedure for issuing unemployment receipts (14pp). (Box 67, Folder 13-14)
    - A (general) 1930-45, Correspondence concerning the State Bar Association's and the Milwaukee Bar Association's conference on labor problems (includes letter from Lloyd K. Garrison); Dr. A.S. Lipschitz's (Representative, Austrian Social-Democracy) request for support for an international protest to release political prisoners; Irving Alexander's case; the organization of technical workers; Isidore Abramowitz's discussion of the Histadrut (n.d.); Bernard Altman's (gas station attendant) discussion of Big Business, men in power, and a statement on war; correspondence from the following organizations: the American Council of Pacific Relations, the Anti-Fascist Literature Committee, Non-Sectarian Anti-Nazi League, Austrian-German Emigree Aid, American Committee International Peace Campaign, Nebraska Writers' Guild (Omaha, Nebraska), American Committee for the Relief of Czecho-Slovak Refugees, Inc.; Ella Fleishman Auerbach forwarding Rabbi S.I. Hillman's (Jerusalem, Palestine) letter (in Hebrew); John Armstrong's (Political Action Committee) "Atomic Age in Action". (Box 67, Folder 15-16)
    - Baerwald, Paul, 1940, Joint Distribution Committee's (JDC) efforts to aid European Jews, with specific concern for Polish Jews. (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Bakery Wagon Drivers and Salesmen Union, Resolution concerning the unity of the AFL and CIO. (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Baldwin, Roger (American Civil Liberties Union) 1932-36, H.R. 6427 (the Kramer sedition bill); H.R. 5845 and S. 2253 (the Military Disaffection Bill); letter to presidential candidates concerning civil rights. (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Baltimore Clothing Manufacturers Association, 1936-39 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Barbash, Jack, 1936 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Barbers and Beauty Cutters of America (National Organizing Committee) 1940, Organizing journeymen barbers and beauty culturists in "Greater New York". (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Barberton Industrial Union Council, 1939 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Barkin, Solomon (Labor Studies Section, Dept. of Commerce) 1936, Recommendation re Henrietta Gross (Barkin's secretary); "liquidation" and replacement of the National Recovery Administration (NRA); H.R. 11554 (the Healy Bill); reference to Solomon Barkin's release. (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Barnes, Harry Elmer, 1932 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Barton, Bruce, 1938 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Barone, Salvatore, 1938, Barone's reply to a charge of anti-Semitism. (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Baruch, Bernard (n.d.) (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Beck, David (Teamsters Union) 1934 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Bedacht, Max (IWO) 1937, Discussion of the reactionary posture of Associated Industries in Montana. (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Bellanca, August, 1935-41 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Bellanca, Dorothy, 1938, Dorothy Bellanca's congressional campaign (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Bellanca, Frank, 1935 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - Benson, Elmer (Minnesota Senator and Governor) 1936-38, H.R. 10189 (American Youth Act) (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Berry, George (Labor's Non-Partisan League) 1934-36, Correspondence regarding the resignation of General Hugh S. Johnson as Administrator of the NRA; the Council for Industrial Progress conference; FDR's re-election; agreement between AFL and Committee on Industrial Organization; Berry's discussion of the establishment of a daily newspaper (8pp.) (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Bevin, Ernest (British Labour Party) 1941 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Biddle, Francis (Labor Disputes Board, and Solicitor General) 1935-40 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Billikopf, Frank (NLRB. Philadelphia Regional Office) 1934-38, Correspondence relating to the Finkelstein case, (including letter from P.B. Young, Journal and Guide) who Billikopf called "one of the most enlightened Negroes"; W.A. White's (Editor and Owner, The Emporia Gazette) discussion of Jim Reed's and Hamilton's (Philadelphia Bulletin) attack on Dubinsky and Hillman; Julian W. Mack's (U.S. Circuit Judge, New York City) discussion of Hillman. (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Biographical Encyclopedia of the World, 1942 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Bisno, Beatrice (N.Y.C. Emergency Relief Bureau) 1938 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Bittner, Van A. (CIO) 1937, General Motors strike (UAW) (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Blinken, S.M. (1937-38), The President's Supreme Court proposals; the American Labor Party of the Eleventh Assembly District; the Maritime Labor Board. (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Bliven, Bruce (New Republic) 1930-36, Bliven's discussion of politics. (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Block, Reuben (Organizer, Allentown, Pa.) 1938 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - Blumberg, Hyman (New York Joint Board) 1936, ACWA retirement benefits; Abraham Cahan's (Editor, Jewish Daily Forward) attack on Hillman and the New York Joint Board's rebuttal. (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Boas, Franz (Anthropologist) 1938, Conference to discuss problems facing Latin American democracies. (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Bond Clothes, 1937-38 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Bookkeepers, Stenographers and Accountants Union, 1936 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Boston Chamber of Commerce, 1941 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - Branden, Maxwell (ACWA attorney) 1938, Opposition to Section 25 of a constitutional amendment requiring court review on facts of all administrative tribunals. (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - Brandeis, Louis, 1937 (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - Bridges, Harry, West Coast Regional Director (CIO) 1938, Includes discussion of the possible relocation of Jack Blumberg from the Los Angeles area; alleged Communist Party member James Mattes; appointees to the Labor Policy Advisory Committee. (Box 68, Folder 36)